"Read and agree with ALL terms of use written in this txt file before using this MikuMikuDance Model Data. If you do not agree with all terms of use, or if you do not understand any part of this terms of use txt file, you are NOT allowed to use this MikuMikuDance Model Data."

"Do not re-distribute this MMD Model Data."

"Please use this MMD Model Data at your own risk. I can not be held liable or responsible for any damages caused by using this data."

"This MMD Model Data may not be used for any works which contain negative content toward the original product, individual, &/or group. "

"You are not allowed to make ANY edits to this MMD Model Data."

"Do not take this Model apart. You are not allowed to create another MMD Model by using parts of this MMD Model Data. (For example, do not take this Model's hair and put it on a different Model.)"

"Do not use this MMD Model for works which include obscene, grotesque, &/or violent content."

"You are NOT permitted to sell this MMD Model data in ANY format, whether digital or in print. This MMD Model data may only be used for non-profit purposes. Do not use this MMD Model data for commercial purposes."

"MikuMikuDance Model created by Peach leaf."

"If you find any works on a NON-JAPANESE website which do not follow these rules, I would greatly appreciate it if you can ask that individual to delete that video &/or image."
